196flavors.com 2018-11-17

# Privacy Policy - 196 flavors

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/196flavors.com).  

196 flavors believes very strongly in keeping your personal information confidential. The following policy describes what information we collect and how it is used and shared.

**Information Collected**  
196 flavors collects as little information as possible from users looking to post comments below our articles. We will typically collect a name (either real or alias), personal website, and email address.

**Cookies / IP Address tracking**  
196 flavors uses cookies to uniquely identify users for the purpose of log files or posting comments. No personal information is stored in these cookies and it is simply a way to identify your computer.

**With Whom Information is Shared**  
None of your information will be shared with third parties. 196 flavors may use your email address in the future to contact you regarding the site, however, an opt-out mechanism will always be provided. Your name and website may be displayed on the site if you post a comment. However, your e-mail address and privacy will always be kept secure.

**Opting Out**  
If 196 flavors chooses to send out newsletter updates in the future and we have your email address on file, you may receive a copy of our newsletter. However, at the bottom of every newsletter will be an easy way to opt out.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.
